You're invited.
Nothing Like a Dame is a documentary film directed by Roger Michell.
BBC Arena's documentary on the Dames of British Theatre and film featuring Maggie Smith, Eileen Atkins, Judi Dench and Joan Plowright on screen
together for the first time as they reminisce over a long summer weekend in a house Joan once shared with Sir Laurence Olivier.
Self, played by Maggie Smith.
Self, played by Judi Dench.
Self, played by Eileen Atkins.
Self, played by Joan Plowright.
Self (archive footage), played by Robert Altman.
Self (archive footage), played by Frank Finlay.
Nothing Like a Dame (released in the United States, Australia and New Zealand as Tea With the Dames) is a 2018
British documentary film directed by Roger Michell, with Sally Angel serving as executive producer.
It was produced by Sally Angel and Karen Steyn with
Maddy Allen as head of production.
The film documents conversations between actresses Eileen Atkins, Judi Dench, Joan Plowright (in her last film appearance), and Maggie Smith (all
of whom are Dames Commander of the Order of the British Empire) interspersed with scenes from their careers on film and stage.
The film explores themes of photographer, photography,
conversation, female friendship, documentary filmmaking.